and to spend a few minutes and talk to
并花几分钟与
you guys about some of the really cool
你们讲一些很酷的
features that are coming inside of STS
STS内置的功能
3.5 designed to support building bigger
3.5设计用于支持更大的建筑
better badder spring boot applications
更好的 spring boot 应用程序
there's a lot of stuff so I'll go ahead
有很多东西，所以我继续
and just art building application file
还有艺术建筑应用文件
new spring starter project gives me a
新的春季入门项目给了我一个
wizard and this wizard lets me choose
向导，这个向导让我选择
the different types of technology
不同类型的技术
verticals I'd like to work with when
我想在什么时候使用的垂直行业
building my application suppose I want
假设我要构建我的应用程序
to build a web application I need only
建立一个我只需要的网络应用程序
check web right if I want to choose from
如果我想选择从网上检查
the workers JPA for example I could as
例如，工人JPA
well or work with JMS or batch or
或与JMS或批处理或
whatever there's a usual pull former
不管有没有平常的拉手
sort of boilerplate this is all metadata
样板，这就是所有元数据
having to do with your project the group
与您的项目有关
ID they are the Maven group ID they made
它们是他们制作的Maven组ID
an artifact ID the description of the
工件ID的描述
project itself etc I can hit next
项目本身，等等，我可以下一步
if I hit next I'm given the URI that I
如果我接下来点击，我会得到我的URI
can visit to to download the zip file
可以访问下载zip文件
but I want or I can just hit finish and
但我想还是可以完成
then STS will go ahead and download the
然后STS将继续下载
zip file unzip it and import it for us
zip文件将其解压缩并为我们导入
on our behalf once we were done with
完成后，代表我们
that we'll have a blank well fairly
我们会相当空白
blank working application complete with
空白的工作申请表完整
an entry point for spring boot spring
spring boot 弹簧的入口
boot of course is our convention over
引导当然是我们的惯例
configuration attention focusing
配置关注焦点
framework for building spring
建筑弹簧的框架
applications first things first I want
我首先要申请的东西
to build some sort of system to manage
建立某种系统来管理
reservations or bookings you know the
预订或您知道的预订
sort of reservation you make in
您进行的某种预订
restaurant or hotel something
餐厅或酒店的东西
nonsensical trivial some first things
琐碎琐碎的第一件事
first I'm going to build a JPA entity
首先，我要建立一个JPA实体
which is going to store my data in the
这会将我的数据存储在
database for me it's going to model a
对我来说，数据库将建模
record as stored in the database rather
记录为存储在数据库中
so class looking like so I want I want
所以班级看起来像我想要我想要
to use the JPA entity annotation but I
使用JPA实体注释，但是我
don't have the entity annotation on my
我的身上没有实体注释
class path spring tool suite is super
类路径 spring tool suite 超级好
smart here it knows that if I hit
聪明的人知道如果我打
control space or command space that I
我控制空间或命令空间
want a the type that's transitively
想要一种可传递的类型
importable through the spring boot
可通过 spring boot 导入
starter data jp8 dependency to be
入门数据jp8依赖关系为
brought in right so again these started
带来了权利，所以这些又开始了
starter dependencies correspond more or
起动器依赖性更多或
less to the checkboxes and that wizard
少了复选框和那个向导
that we looked at earlier and so when I
我们之前看过，所以当我
chose to
选择
import the ad entity annotation and the
导入广告实体注释和
type that contains it spring tool suite
包含它的类型Spring工具套件
was smart enough to automatically add
足够聪明，可以自动添加
this dependency for me as though I had
对我来说，这种依赖
chosen the checkbox upfront and the
先选择了复选框，然后
wizard you know so if you want to start
向导知道，所以如果您想开始
coding you want to want to work and you
您想要工作的编码，而您
don't have to worry about dependencies
不必担心依赖关系
just go for it
就去吧
again spring tool suite will will help
spring tool suite 将再次帮助
you make up the difference later on okay
你以后补好差价
so now I've got a basic entity a basic
所以现在我有一个基本实体
class I'm going to give it a primary key
我要给它一个主键
right so at ID like so command you know
对，所以在ID这样的命令，你知道
hitting command ship down there at
在这里命中指挥舰
generated value control space and then a
生成值控制空间，然后
need a field for the reservation name of
需要一个字段作为预订名称
course and then from here I'm going to
当然，然后从这里我要
use the quick access support the really
使用快速访问支持
really smart quick access support to
真正智能的快速访问支持
generate some stuff for me so generate
为我产生一些东西，所以产生
constructor please I don't want to the
构造函数，请不要
ID in my constructor but a regular would
我的构造函数中的ID，但常规会
be fine I want a generate a constructor
很好，我想生成一个构造函数
from superclass that's fine because you
来自超类，那很好，因为你
need a no arguing constructor for JPA of
需要一个无争议的JPA构造函数
course like so and then I need a Gators
当然是这样，然后我需要一个鳄鱼
select Gators okay voila and then just
选择鳄鱼好吧瞧瞧，然后
for good form you need a two string
为了获得良好的形式，您需要两个字符串
right so I'll go ahead and generate that
对，所以我继续进行
as well and with that we have a basic JP
以及因此，我们有一个基本的JP
entity now we'll use spring data to work
实体现在我们将使用spring数据来工作
with that JP entity so booking
该JP实体的预订
repository extends JP a repository
知识库扩展了JP知识库
alright so it's going to be a JP
好吧，这将是一个JP
repository for entities of type booking
类型预订实体的存储库
with ID type long and this repository at
ID类型为long且此存储库位于
a minimum will support read update
最低将支持读取更新
delete style uh work but we can also add
删除样式，但我们也可以添加
finder methods for example collection
查找器方法示例集合
looking fine by booking name string
预订名称字符串看起来不错
booking name okay and which command ship
预订名称是否正确以及哪个指挥舰
them to bring make sure we have all the
他们带来确保我们拥有所有
types that we need in the class path
我们在类路径中需要的类型
again never keeping our focus from the
再次永远不要把我们的注意力从
line of code that we're on right now and
我们现在正在使用的代码行
with that we have the working we have
有了我们，我们有了工作
the pieces let's go ahead and you know
碎片让我们继续前进，您知道
to their paces right so build a little
按照他们的步伐，所以建立一些
component here that will be invoked when
此处将在以下时间调用的组件
the application starts up and given the
该应用程序启动并给定
command-line arguments so booking
命令行参数所以要预约
command line letter implements command
命令行字母实现命令
line runner like so of course I need to
像这样的线路赛跑者当然我需要
import the type right so that does this
正确导入类型，以便执行此操作
come in three override implement methods
引入三种替代实现方法
hit command line winner choose run okay
命中命令行优胜者选择运行正常
and from here we have everything we need
从这里我们有我们需要的一切
to actually kind of work with it except
实际使用它，除了
for one thing a database and data in the
一方面，数据库和数据
database here to swing boot can help so
摆动启动的数据库可以帮助您
we need either to explicitly configure a
我们需要明确配置
data source or to provide the requisite
数据源或提供必要条件
in-memory embedded database jars so that
内存嵌入式数据库jar，以便
spring boot can automatically
spring boot 可以自动
instantiate one for us here to swing
实例化一个供我们摇摆
tool Suites smarts can help us out so go
智慧工具套件可以帮助我们解决问题
to the Maven editor and you can do this
到Maven编辑器，您可以执行此操作
either in the dependencies sub tab down
在依赖项子选项卡中
here or you can just do it in line right
在这里，或者您可以直接在右行
either ones fine comm h2 database i
两者都很好comm h2数据库我
always forget the coordinates right so
总是忘记坐标，所以
again spring tool suite can be
再次 spring tool suite 可以
invaluable here I can choose a just
宝贵的我可以在这里选择一个
chosen the group ID in the artifact ID I
在工件ID I中选择了组ID
can specify the version if I'd like of
如果需要，可以指定版本
course it's smart enough to know I could
当然，它足够聪明，知道我可以
even just specify the property because
甚至只是指定属性，因为
it knows about the effective property
它知道有效属性
defined by the spring boot parent palm
由 spring boot 父母掌定义
right but again since it's already
是的，但是又一次，因为它已经
defined by the parent problem I don't
由我没有定义的父级问题
need it I no longer need to explicitly
需要它，我不再需要明确
provide it here unless I want to
除非我想在这里提供
override it what I have here is the palm
覆盖它我在这里的是手掌
that spring boot provides that has all
spring boot 提供了一切
the versions for all the different
所有不同版本
libraries you're likely to kind of
您可能会喜欢的库
likely going to use already described
可能会使用已经描述过的
and tested and integrated together so if
并测试并集成在一起，因此如果
you wanna use JPA and spring MVC and
您想使用JPA和spring MVC以及
spring data spring that spring
spring data 那年春天
innovation all these other pieces and
创新所有这些其他方面，
you wonder which logging or API which
您想知道哪个日志记录或API
version should I use wonder no more it's
我应该不再使用的版本了
all already taken care of for you move
所有已经照顾好你的举动
to our application move to our code and
我们的应用程序移到我们的代码，
it'll start up and it'll create a data
它会启动并创建数据
source for us but that doesn't solve the
源给我们，但这不能解决
old problem of you know not having any
你的老问题知道没有
data in our
我们的数据
bass so let's go ahead and create a new
低音，让我们继续创造一个新的
folder okay file new folder demo source
文件夹好的文件新文件夹演示源
main resources like so and we'll put a
这样的主要资源，我们将
new file in there called data that
那里的新文件称为数据
sequel which spring boot will pick up at
spring boot 会在哪里续集
the beginning of the of the run and
运行的开始和
it'll automatically insert the DDL that
它会自动插入
it finds in a file called schema DEP
它在名为schema DEP的文件中找到
sequel and it'll automatically insert
续集，它将自动插入
the data that it finds inside of a file
它在文件内部找到的数据
called data EPS equal for us so insert
所谓的数据EPS对我们来说相等，所以插入
into okay okay name values Chris Martin
进入ok好的名称值Chris Martin
and Josh alrighty and with that in place
和乔希·好吧，有了这个
hit command 3 again so that in place
再次命中命令3
that's hit command 3 run spring boot
命中命令3运行spring boot
application that'll start it up over
重新启动它的应用程序
here go ahead and put that down there
这里继续把它放在那里
and you'll see the application get
然后您会看到该应用程序得到
started you'll see the tables
开始，您将看到表格
automatically created and the data
自动创建和数据
should be there as well we can verify as
应该在那里，我们可以验证为
much by simply injecting our
只需注入我们的他妈的就可以了
repository here like so and then running
这样存储库，然后运行
through it so for booking be working
通过它，以便预订工作
repository that find all command 3-1
查找所有命令3-1的存储库
and there you go you can see the output
然后您可以看到输出
data reflecting exactly the day that we
数据恰好反映了我们这一天
put in there already as a last step
作为最后一步已经放在那里
let's go ahead and you know take this to
让我们继续前进，您知道将其带到
the edge of the web they say that any
他们说，在网络的边缘
application of sufficient complexity
足够复杂的应用
eventually it sends email I posit that
最终它发送电子邮件，我认为
any application of sufficient complexity
任何具有足够复杂性的应用
also exposes the REST API so rest a
还公开了REST API，因此请
booking rest control that has one job
预订一项工作的休息控制
and is to return all the bookings in the
并返回所有的预订
database to the client right so I'm will
数据库对客户端的权利，所以我会
return this dot voila request mapping
返回此点瞧请求映射
bookings and add the spring for at rest
预订并添加春季休息
controller notation and we're off so we
控制器符号，我们离开了，所以我们
have a now a spring MVC REST API a
现在有了spring MVC REST API
powered by or you know working with data
由供电或您知道使用数据
that's driven by a spring data
由弹簧数据驱动
repository and then we have a spring
仓库，然后我们有了一个春天
boot command line writer that prints out
打印出来的引导命令行编写器
as well and the application startup and
以及应用程序启动和
a spring boot entry point as well as a
spring boot 入口点以及
JPA entity so we'll stop this command 3
JPA实体，所以我们将停止此命令3
run it again
再次运行
yeah data prints out on the client on
是的，数据在客户端上打印出来
the command line just as before but now
命令行与以前一样，但现在
for the in in STS browser HTTP localhost
在STS浏览器HTTP本地主机中
colon 8080 both games hit go and you can
冒号8080这两款游戏都打了，你可以
see the response coming back from the
看到响应从
database you can also see the query
数据库中您还可以看到查询
that's being issued on our behalf so
是代表我们发行的
again got a lot a lot a lot of stuff
再有很多很多的东西
done very very quickly you know one
很快就知道了
might wonder just how we're doing all
可能想知道我们如何做的一切
this like where where are we setting up
就像我们在哪里设置
spring MVC where where's a the spring
Spring MVC春天在哪里
data stuff being you know set up and all
您知道的数据设置以及所有
that this is all being provided by
这都是由
spring boot there's no magic here this
spring boot 这里没有魔术
is just a sort of Auto configuration
只是一种自动配置
that you can come to expect from spring
你可以期待春天
boot it itself is in turn using Springs
启动它本身就是使用Springs
Java configuration which means that if
Java配置，这意味着
you want to figure out what spring boot
您想弄清楚什么是 spring boot
is doing you need to look no further
在做你不需要再看了
than the spring tools live beans graph
比spring tool活 bean 图
view this will show you all the beans
查看这将显示所有 Bean type
that have been configured in your spring
在您的弹簧中配置的
application as well as the dependencies
应用程序以及依赖项
that they have so here's the HTV message
他们有，所以这是HTV讯息
converters Auto configuration class
转换器自动配置类
that's provided by spring boot that in
这是由Spring Boot提供的
turn depends on this oddly named
转向取决于这个奇怪的名字
configuration properties you'll see that
配置属性，您将看到
in several different places but for
在几个不同的地方，但是
example the dispatcher servlet auto
调度程序servlet自动示例
configuration class has a subclass
配置类有一个子类
called dispatcher servlet configuration
称为调度程序servlet配置
which itself depends on server
这本身取决于服务器
properties server properties is a
属性服务器属性是
configuration properties annotated class
配置属性注释的类
that is used by spring boot to load all
spring boot 用于加载所有
properties having to do with the
与...有关的属性
configuration of the server the web
Web服务器的配置
server in this case Tomcat or Jenny
在这种情况下为服务器Tomcat或Jenny
overview that's used in an embedded case
嵌入式案例中使用的概述
all these properties are expected to
所有这些特性都有望
start with a string server dot so server
以字符串服务器点开始，因此服务器
dot port server dot address server dot
点端口服务器点地址服务器点
session timeout etc this can be very
会话超时等，这可能非常
useful for finding ways to override a
寻找替代方法的有用
customized spring boots behavior at
定制的 spring boot 行为
runtime this graph gives you all that
运行时，该图为您提供了所有
access there are different ways of
访问有不同的方式
looking at it I like the graph view just
看着它，我喜欢图视图
as much as the tree view they're both
和树视图一样多
very handy in different situations here
在不同情况下非常方便
this shows you the code page of the
这将显示您的代码页
class rather and the beam that's defined
类而不是定义的光束
in that class so foreign to get the
在那个班级如此外国
details and want to see what's happening
细节，想看看发生了什么
and you'd only double-click and you'll
然后您只需双击即可
see what's happening
看看发生了什么
again the nice thing about this is you
再次这件事的好处是你
can see the relationships you can see
可以看到你可以看到的关系
everything you don't have to guess I
一切你不必猜我
think that about covers it I would
认为涵盖它我会
remind people that I'm spring that io4
提醒人们我是io4的春天
slash guides there's a bevy of tailored
斜线指南中有大量的量身定制的
guides task-focused
指导以任务为中心
guides that show you how to do a given
指导您如何做给定的
thing in 10 to 15 minutes to use them
10至15分钟内即可使用它们
you go to file new import spring getting
你去申请新的进口春季
started content and these guides are you
入门内容，这些指南就是您
can follow them along inside of STS they
可以跟随他们在STS内部
also mostly build on top of boots if you
如果您愿意的话，也大多建立在靴子上
wanted to follow to toriel learn how to
想跟着去学习如何
work with Twitter or not learn how to
使用Twitter或不了解如何
work with Facebook or rabbim Q or Redis
与Facebook或rabbim Q或Redis合作
or or any of the other things that you
或您的其他任何东西
can do with them
可以和他们一起做
spring and spring boot then go ahead
春天和 spring boot ，然后继续
write just go to this type this dialog
写只是去这种类型的这个对话框
choose one choose the build type write
选择一种，选择构建类型
maven or Gradle are supported by default
默认情况下支持Maven或Gradle
and then choose which code set you want
然后选择所需的代码集
to use so add the box for example you'll
使用，所以添加例如框，您将
get the initial working project which is
得到最初的工作项目是
basically an empty skeletal directory
基本上是一个空的骨架目录
structure and then you'll get the
结构，然后您将获得
complete project which contains the
完整的项目，其中包含
finished project that you can follow
您可以关注的已完成项目
along
沿